[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred in the 1987 comedy movie Raising Arizona?", "correct_answer": "Nicolas Cage", "incorrect_answers": ["Faye Dunaway", "Bruce Willis", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the Turkish Airlines Flight 981 McDonnell Douglas DC-10 crash on On March 3, 1974?", "correct_answer": "Close to Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["Nearby Rome", "Nearby London", "Istanbul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Voltaic pile, known as the first modern electric battery, was invented by Alessandro Volta in what year?", "correct_answer": "1800", "incorrect_answers": ["1459", "1890", "1902"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who were two of Spicolis stoner buds in the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High?", "correct_answer": "Anthony Edwards and Eric Stoltz", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicolas Cage and Forrest Whittaker", "Eric Stoltz and Forrest Whittaker", "Forrest Whittaker and Anthony Edwards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the school bus driver in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "Helen", "incorrect_answers": ["Alyssa", "Gwen", "Helga"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why dont you wish in one hand and s**t in the other. See which one fills up first is a line from which movie?", "correct_answer": "Bad Santa", "incorrect_answers": ["The Cable Guy", "Kings of Comedy", "How High"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of this thick noodle made of egg and flour means little ribbon in Italian. It is very popular in Rome and is similar to what is called tagliatelle elsewhere in Italy.", "correct_answer": "fettuccine", "incorrect_answers": ["farfallone", "fiorentine", "orecchiette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Herbie from the movie The Love Bug, is a special car with a mind of its own. Do you know what kind of car Herbie was?", "correct_answer": "Volkswagen Beetle", "incorrect_answers": ["Mini Cooper", "Aston Martin DB5", "Ford Mustang"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do Troy Bolton and Gabriella Montez meet in the film High School Musical?", "correct_answer": "at a New Years Eve party", "incorrect_answers": ["at a bar", "at school", "at a Thanksgiving party"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which New York City borough is Central Park located?", "correct_answer": "Manhattan", "incorrect_answers": ["Queens", "Bronx", "Brooklyn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Pink Panther from the 2006 comedy movie The Pink Panther?", "correct_answer": "A pink diamond", "incorrect_answers": ["A private detective", "The stage name of a female performer", "A rare pink cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This group of alloys, which is a combination of at least one metal and one or more other elements, is used to clad fuel rods in nuclear plants.", "correct_answer": "Zircaloy", "incorrect_answers": ["Amalgam", "Hastelloy", "Electrum"]}]